

## CONTACT



203-727-3577



williambrendanhenry@yahoo.com



4 Strathmore Avenue, Milford, CT, 06461

## SKILLS

- PROFESSIONAL
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Social Media Marketing
- SAP & Kronos
- Human Resources
- Conflict Resolution
- Retail Management
- Corporate Training
- Cinemark Scholarship Recipient
- Interned with Disney for 2 Summers

#### EDUCATION

MFA | CREATIVE WRITING
Western CT State University | Danbury
2019 – 2020

BACHELOR'S | ENGLISH, MINOR: HISTORY Southern CT State University | New Haven 2013 -2018

# WILLIAM HENRY

SELF-DIRECTED VIRTUOSO WITH DIVERSE SKILLS

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Highly motivated and energetic hands-on individual. Has been given autonomy to make decisions in multiple roles, as well as manage teams. Consistently demonstrates efficient time management and selected to train colleagues on company procedures. Has a strong track record of managerial and leadership qualities. Published materials on two different educational websites.

### RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

#### STORE TRAINER AND ASSISTANT HR MANAGER

Boscov's | Milford, CT | Jul 2018- May 2020

Directed all new hires and provided ongoing training on register procedures and company-specific policies. Promoted after store opening in October 2018 to Staff Scheduler, Assistant Human Resource Manager, and Acting Furniture Manager. Created and generated staffing schedule based on projected business needs. Assisted in cash office to resolve overages and shortages. Worked in absence of receiving manager to ensure shipment was distributed properly, while implementing safety protocols.

#### MEN'S AND BOY'S RECEIVING LEAD

Old Navy | Milford, CT | Aug 2008- Oct 2018

Assisted customers in finding merchandise and explaining store policies. Trusted to work independently during the overnight shift to handle diverse technology-related and merchandising tasks. Oversaw the receiving process and team during the early morning shift to ensure product was available for customers to ensure company success. Was recruited to assist with remodeling six locations based on leadership skills and retail knowledge.

#### ASSISTANT DATA COORDINATOR

Linda McMahon for Senate | North Haven, CT | Jul 2012- Nov 2012

Worked closely with Data coordinator in specially created position based on skillset. Set up call centers and databases at thirteen locations around the state. Worked autonomously and managed a team of 35 interns who canvassed specific territories based on Map Point generated routes. Created Excel sheets for tracking responses from voters and for lawn sign distribution.